kiacerritos.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy of Kia of Cerritos

**Privacy Policy **1\. Collection of Personal Information**   
Within this website, Kia and/or the dealer may seek certain personal information provided by the visitor for the purpose of sending product brochures or promotional materials. Information such as name, mailing address, e-mail address, type of request, and any additional information you provide, is collected by Kia and is used to meet your request. The information you provide is used by Kia to improve the services we provide to you. Your information is never given or sold to any third parties.  **

**

**2\. No Guarantee of Confidential Use of Website**   
Kia cannot guarantee your confidential use of this website. Kia will not assume responsibility for any damage you or any person may suffer as a result of a breach of confidentiality resulting from your use of this site or any information you transmitted to this site. 

**3\. Hypertext Links**   
This site may contain hypertext links to other websites. Kia makes no representation or warranty as to the accuracy of any information contained in any such hypertext link. Any hypertext link to any other person or entity should not be construed as endorsement by Kia of such person's or entity's website, products or services. Your linking to other off-site pages or other sites is at your own risk. 

**4\. Copyright/Trademark Ownership**   
The information in this site is protected by copyright. You may only use the information, text or graphics contained in this site for your personal use and may not reproduce, adapt, or publish it, in whole or in part, for any purpose without the consent of Kia. The Kia mark and design are registered trademarks of Kia Motors Corporation of Korea. The Kia mark and design may not be used, downloaded, copied or distributed in any way. 

**5\. Assent to Privacy Policy**   
By using this site, you agree to the terms of the Kia Website Privacy Policy as set forth above. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this website. Kia reserves the right to change any of its Website Privacy Policies at any time.

**
